No, sir, I haven't been a part of any discussions on that.
All right, go ahead.
In the ceasefire...
This is CNN speaking, by the way, so...
Are you personally participating?
Yeah, this is one of the worst reporters that you'll ever...
I don't even want to take a question.
It's a waste of time.
Go ahead.
How will you decide which workers get back pay and which workers do not?
Well, we're going to see.
Some are going to get back pay, and we're going to try and make sure of that.
But some of them are being hurt very badly by the Democrats,
and they, therefore, won't qualify.
Go ahead, please.
What will the administration do to foreign Antifa organizers and funders
who are located overseas?
Go ahead, in the yellow, please.